### **Stephen Jackson**

37 Manchester Road Audenshaw Manchester M34 5PZ

Telephone: 07925 507 062 Email: stevie1311@outlook.com

### Professional profile

I'm a highly competent, motivated, and enthusiastic individual who is persistent when it comes to achieving goals and never backs down when rising to new challenges.

I possess the ability to generate and innovate ideas and solutions to problems. I'm willing to undertake further training and seeking to develop my career. I'm flexible and adaptable with proven problem-solving skills and a keen eye for detail.

I'm quick to learn and eager to advance.

### **Key Skills**

Systems Knowledge: Experience in supporting, Active Directory, LAN Admin, Microsoft applications and many inhouse applications.

Team player: Enjoys sharing knowledge and encouraging others to develop.

Communication: Excellent customer services skills. Deals with internal & external customers at all levels via telephone and e-mail to ensure a successful resolution of their issue.

Problem solving: Resolves issues in a methodical manner, independently and with internal/external support teams.

Planning and organising: Refined planning and organisation skills that balance work, team support and ad-hoc responsibilities in a timely & professional manner.

### Career summary

career summary	
June 2022 – July 2022	CodeNation, Manchester, Training course.
	Completed a 3 week course covering the coding basics of Python, HTML & CSS. I'm currently continuing learning on my own time using online tutorials.
May 2008 – December 2020	The Co-Operative Group/Tata Consultancy Services, IT Service Desk Analyst.
	Working on the IT Service Desk providing overnight support to all parts of the business, in particular providing support to the Distribution Centres. Overnight we provided 1st line support for Remote access, Microsoft applications, Manhattan, Cordis, AS400, Citrix and various other depot based applications, also the creation of and amending accounts.

September 2007 - May 2008

Probation Service, (Contractor, (Addeco)), Hyde, Receptionist.

Working at the Probation Service's Hyde office, my duties included meeting and greeting visitors, answering incoming telephone calls, copy & audio typing and preparing outgoing post for collection.

September 2005 - July 2007

Fujitsu – LloydsTSB, Bristol, IT Service Desk Analyst.

Working on the back-office side of the Bristol service desk, my duties included, closing calls, managing engineers workloads, providing advice to colleagues, chasing/escalating calls with Engineers and Team leaders, logging calls with 3<sup>rd</sup> parties, taking 1<sup>st</sup> line calls from customers, providing 1<sup>st</sup> line fixes or forwarding details to on-site engineers.

December 2004 – September 2005

Sulzer Pumps, (Contractor, Esprit People)), Manchester, Administratior.

Working at their Manchester factory, I was responsible for the sorting, scanning, archiving of 30 years worth of paper files.

June 2003 - December 2004

Royal & Sun Alliance, Manchester Diocese Board of Finance, Sesame Ltd and Hepworth Building Products, (Contractor, (Spring Personnel,)) Manchester, administration.

I held various positions ranging from administration assistant to receptionist. All the contracts were short term with no chance of permanent employment.

November 2002 - May 2003

Royal & Sun Alliance and IKEA, (Contractor (Primetime Recruitment,)), Manchester, administration.

I held various positions ranging from administration assistant to receptionist. All the contracts were short term with no chance of permanent employment.

June 2002 - November 2002

Standguide Ltd., Manchester, training course.

I undertook a training course in Microsoft Office, which led to a CLAIT certificate. The course covered all aspects of MS Word, MS Excel and MS Access.

April 1994 – May 2000

Airtours Holidays Ltd., Hemlshore, Customer Services Assistant.

Working in the Customer Services department, I was responsible for the turnaround of incoming mail, scanning documents onto their image and workflow system, registering new and updating ongoing complaints, and taking incoming calls from customers and preparing reports for management and resort offices.

November 1993 – November 1994

DDI Manchester Ltd. Manchester, Business Administration course.

I undertook a training course in Business Administration, which led to a NVQ level 2 qualification. The course covered all aspects of the office environment, including computer applications, filing, faxing, photocopying, petty cash, stock control, mail handling, written communications, etc...

May 1992 – October 1992

Specialised Training Services Ltd., Manchester, Business Administration course.

I helped write a book on the history of Manchester, this included, research methods, computer applications (WordStar and timeworks publisher,) photography and creative writing.

January 1990 - July 1990

Company: Casinos Austria Ltd. (Prague), Croupier.

Working within a busy casino, my duties included dealing and inspecting American roulette and blackjack. I was responsible for counting cash, paperwork, handling disputes with customers, keeping records, staff rotas, Pit Boss duties, and ensuring the smooth running of the casino.

January 1989 – December 1989

Stakis, Stockport, Croupier.

Working within a busy casino, my duties included dealing and inspecting American roulette, blackjack and punto banco. I was responsible for counting cash, paperwork, handling disputes with customers, keeping records, staff rotas, Pit Boss duties, and ensuring the smooth running of the casino.

January 1989 – December 1989

Pleasurama plc, Manchester, Croupier.

Working within a busy casino, my duties included dealing and inspecting American roulette, blackjack and punto banco. I was responsible for counting cash, paperwork, handling disputes with customers, keeping records, staff rotas, Pit Boss duties, and ensuring the smooth running of the casino.

# **Education & qualifications**

#### St Gregory's RC High School 1975 – 1980

- > C.S.E. Mathematics
- > C.S.E. English
- > C.S.E. Chemistry
- > C.S.E. Physics
- > C.S.E. Geography
- > C.S.E. Metalwork

#### **DDI Manchester LTD.**

> NVQ level 2 Business Administration

## References available on request